Viewers, God’s time is the best.
Any moment from now, we shall be ushered into the New Year.
Happy New Year!
What is New Year?
What do we understand by year – ‘New Year’?
It is a gift from God – a part of the divine nature of God.
In the New Year, you are called to God’s kind of lifestyle – I mean, His divine essence
in terms of faithfulness, steadfastness and love.
Love your neighbour as yourself.
It is all about God – the New Year.
If it is all about God, nothing of God can be possible unless our heart is pure.
In the Book of Matthew 5:8, Christ tells us, “Blessed are the pure in heart for they shall see God”.
Christianity lies in the heart.
It is all about heart.
What is the position of your heart?
Are you holding grudges?
When you hold grudges against a brother, you have already grieved the Holy Spirit.
Nothing good can come.
Viewers, let us pray.
Whatever barrier between you and the Spirit of God – be removed, in the name of Jesus Christ!
As you enter the New Year, whatever barrier between you and the Spirit of God -
be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever wall between you and the Spirit of God – be removed, in the name of Jesus!
I want to believe that your relationship with God has been re-established.
Yes.
In the New Year 2018, your relationship with God has been re-established.
Whatever wall, whatever barrier between you and the Spirit of the Father -
be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Let there be a relationship between you and God, in Jesus Christ’s name!
Viewers, Happy New Year!
I want to let you know right now,
every unfavourable situation you have been in, in the year 2017 has been ended with the year!
Every unfavourable situation in your business, career, marriage and family -
cease, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Unfavourable situation in your health,
whatever challenges you are facing in your blood, fluids, tendons,
in your way, in the name of Jesus!
At the command of Jesus, Peter walked on the sea.
At the command of Jesus, Blind Bartimaeus received his sight.
I command every unfavourable situation you have been in, in the year 2017 -
cease and end with 2017!
You are ushered into the New Year, 2018.
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, my brothers!
Happy New Year, once again!
This is the voice of God to you.
Happy New Year!
This is the right time and the Word you are receiving is from the throne of God.
Yes.
Happy New Year, once again!
Yes, I know you are expecting many things from me - the message and the prophecy for the New Year.
Yes, God's time is the best.
I want to assure you that this message will be delivered at God's appropriate time.
HAPPY NEW BEGINNING
On Behalf Of T.B. Joshua And Emmanuel TV Family